myfreevod.com 2014-12-12

# MYFREEPAYSITE.COM - PRIVACY POLICY

**The[MyFreePaysite.com](http://www.myfreepaysite.com/) Privacy Policy**

We take your privacy seriously.  Read this page to learn about our privacy policy.

|   
---|---  
  
**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how MyFreePaysite.com treats personal information and e-mail addresses that MyFreePaysite.com collects and receives. The only personal information we collect is your e-mail address

. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MyFreePaysite.com does not own or control, or to people that MyFreePaysite.com does not employ or manage.

**General**

MyFreePaysite.com only collects and stores your e-mail address when you register for MyFreePaysite.com membership access and the MyFreePaysite.com blacklist. We do not collect your e-mail address under any other circumstances.

MyFreePaysite.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MyFreePaysite.com cookie information, and the page you request. Except in emergencies dealing with fraud, we do not connect this general internet traffic data with your specific e-mail address.

MyFreePaysite.com uses information for the following general purposes:

  * Your e-mail address is used to contact you on a transactional basis. More specifically, we will send you an e-mail when you sign up for your membership, choose to cancel it, or request that your password be sent to you in case you have forgotten it.

  * Your e-mail address is used to send you our newsletter featuring website updates. This newsletter is generally sent every 30-90 days.

MyFreePaysite.com does not rent, sell, or share your personal information or e-mail address with any third-parties. The only persons with access to your e-mail address are trusted high-level MyFreePaysite.com employees.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information or email address as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MyFreePaysite.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if MyFreePaysite.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MyFreePaysite.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

This privacy statement covers the website http://www.myfreepaysite.com and all pages on its domain name. When you click a link or otherwise leave this domain name, our privacy policy will no longer apply.

Our website may participate in co-branding agreements which use the MyFreePaysite.com brand name, domain name, or the general "look and feel" of our site to work with another company.  In these cases, your personally identifiable information will be NOT be shared with our co-branding partners. Our privacy policy will not be applicable in such cases; however, we will require that our partners post their own company name and privacy policy at the bottom of any co-branded site.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We may use cookies on this site but we do NOT link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use only session ID cookies which make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. We do NOT use persistent cookies which remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but you may have to re-enter your username and password more often and you may experience some other unexpected browsing inconveniences. 

Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MyFreePaysite.com's cookies.

**Third Party Cookies**

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility companies, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement.  We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility companies, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

**Your Ability to Access, Edit and Delete Your Personal Information and E-mail Address**

As part of your membership, you are required to keep a current e-mail address on file with MyFreePaysite.com where we may send you transaction-based e-mails as well as our monthly newsletter.

If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from receiving our e-mails, you must delete your account with MyFreePaysite.com. There are 2 ways in which you can delete your account:

1) You may click on the Delete Account link at the bottom of every e-mail communication from MyFreePaysite.com.

2) You may login to the MyFreePaysite.com Members Area and click the Delete My Account link.

In both cases, you will receive one final e-mail confirmation that your account has been deleted and you will never be contacted again for any reason. 

If you have any further questions about your personally identifiable information or email address changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may contact us by e-mail or postal mail at the information at the bottom of this page.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and e-mail addresses submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information and e-mail address, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We limit access to you personal information and e-mail address to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information.

**Minors**

MyFreePaysite.com is an adult site and access to persons under the age of 18 is strictly prohibited. MyFreePaysite.com has no intention of collecting any personally-identifiable information from individuals under eighteen years of age. MyFreePaysite.com specifically instruct minors not to submit such information on our website. If a minor has provided us with personally-identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that minor should contact us using the contact form listed at the bottom of this page and we will remove this information from our existing files.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

MyFreePaysite.com may update this policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information or e-mail addresses by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MyFreePaysite.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Changes in E-Mail Practices**

If we decide to make changes in our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make material changes to the way we use your email address, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**About Our Blog**

MyFreePaysite.com operates a blog at [http://blog.myfreepasyite.com](http://blog.myfreepasyite.com/) where users are able to leave comments that are publicly posted for other users to read.

If you use the blog on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in the blog.

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial  

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at: 

Online: [Contact Form](http://www.myfreepaysite.com/contact.html)

MyFreePaysite.com  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
2123 Warwick Lane  
Glenview, IL 60026  
USA

Effective Date: August 22, 2008

* * *

**If you have any questions, please[contact us](http://www.myfreepaysite.com/contact.html). Thanks!**
